And yet she did grant my wish.
Holding up her end of this perverse contract, I suppose.
And I became an eternal girl.
To repeat the cycle.
Get it now?
That's the ugly truth behind this game!
He's away!
Oh my gosh! Are you okay?
Ruko!
Go get help! Call an ambulance!
But I don't have a cell phone!
Come on, think!
Hitoi has one! Just hurry!
What? Oh, right!
It's fine.
An election or anything.
Willi's world may begin.
You don't remember the Ar Wild processes.
I'm super jealous.
I gave her flash.
May have%.
It's IU's history men who will believe you
after a trip.
It's alright!
It's not THAT CHADCasEhe.
Thank you.
Yeah, nothing serious. The doctor said she's stable now.
Uh-huh. Yeah, they called them. I hope this is okay. But I, uh, I wanted to wait with Hitaway a bit longer. You know, until her parents show up, at least.
Sure. That's fine. Of course you can stay with your friend. I'm just glad you called. But how are you?
I'm worried.
No, don't. I'll be okay. I'll call again if anything else comes up.
Mm-hmm.
Why didn't I listen to you?
I should have stopped when I had the chance.
Oh, Yuzuki. Do you know how this happened?
I think so. I won the battle and then... Well, it was strange.
And now...
You become an Elric.
Where am I?
What's going on here?
Nice to meet you.
Yuzuki.
Who are you?
My name is...
Mayu.
That's insane.
It was like some sort of weird initiation.
She told me all about selectors, Elrigs, and how Eternal Girls work.
If you become an Elrig, then apparently you wake up there.
You think Hanayu went through the same thing?
I would imagine so.
Mayu. A white room.
Tama, do you know something?
My memory is still too fuzzy.
So who is this Mayu girl?
I don't know. She didn't talk about herself much.
I see.
I know what you're thinking.
That Hanayu was tricking me this entire time.
She didn't mention a word about her taking my place or any of that.
If what Mayu told me is true, she's out there living my life right now.
All that talk about helping me with my wish.
Figured she was laughing at me the whole time.
Don't say that!
Well, that's what I thought.
But...
Hanayu...
How could you do this?
We were friends!
Don't blame her.
Elrigs are not allowed to share the truth with their selectors.
Why do you know this and nobody else?
What is this place?
What the hell are you?
If this rule is broken, if their selector learns the truth and refuses to battle anymore,
that Elrig will forever lose her chance to escape the world inside her card.
Then you're doing it too.
You're trying to trick...
Poor Hitoye.
It's not that simple.
I'll try to explain.
Nice to meet you, selector.
I couldn't believe it.
Hitoye became a selector again and I was her Elrig.
I didn't know what to do.
Should I hide the truth from her?
Was it my job to force her into battle?
At the very least, I knew I'd be stuck in this card if I didn't.
But after what happened...
Let's be friends, Hitoye.
How do...
How do you know my name?
Who are you?
Well, let's just say I'm magic, okay?
Even though we didn't know her for long,
I still felt like we were good friends.
But after her wish was corrupted,
she really did forget about us.
I'm your Elrig now, so take good care of me.
Elrig?
What?
For starters, can you tell me your wish?
My wish?
Yeah, if you have one, I can make it come true.
I'm Yuzuki, by the way.
I think you and I will be good friends.
You.
Su.
Ki.
I've gotta fight my way out of here.
Even if I have to hurt Hitoye to do it,
I need to see Kazuki again.
That was all I could think.
Hey, don't be shy.
You must have a wish.
I don't know.
Hitoye?
You okay?
Did something happen?
Talk to me, Hitoye.
Please!
I knew her wish was already dead.
But what could I do?
This was the only chance given to me.
I had to take it.
But then...
Just as I was starting to think I'd have to give up,
I guess I got lucky and...
Something happened.
I guess I got lucky and something happened.
Let's go.
Hitoye?
Oh my gosh, are you okay?
If it hurts, why are you putting yourself through this?
I don't know why. I just feel like this is something important.
But I think maybe I do have a wish.
I want to have friends. And for some reason, that hurts.
After all the horrible things she went through, all that pain and confusion,
she still asks for the same thing.
Can I have friends? Can you do that?
You have my word. I promise I'll make your wish come true.
How could I say no to a crying girl, you know?
Whether it was right or not, I guess I got caught up in the moment.
Will Hitoy's wish turn out like mine?
Even if I can make it come true, is it really worth the cost?
It makes me wonder if Hanayou went through all this too.
I wonder if she felt as lost and hurt as I do now.
And if her wish came true...
Harayou...
After that, I started to rethink things.
Hey, Hito-e?
If you want your wish to come true, we'll have to find a battle.
Okay, I'll try.
I intentionally had her battle you.
And then told you the truth in front of her.
So it's not quite what it looked like.
I was hoping she'd refuse to fight after she heard that.
But if she quit, then you'd be stuck in the cart forever, wouldn't you?
That doesn't matter.
She's my friend.
If I have to sacrifice her, then I might as well just disappear.
And besides, if I can't live as Yuzuki Kurabayashi anymore,
if I can't even love Kazuki as myself anymore,
then what's the point?
I give up.
Yuzuki?
Hito-e?
Uh, hello!
Oh, Ruko!
Where's Hito-e? Is she okay?
Uh, yeah, everything is just fine.
Mostly, at least.
Seems like she's calmed down now.
The doctor's with her.
You can go inside.
Oh, no.
I'm alright.
I'm just scared.
Hito-e was...
She was so sweet before.
But now I don't know what's going on in her head.
It's terrifying.
What am I supposed to do?
What can I do?
It's like...
I don't even know her anymore.
I'm at a loss.
Um...
Hey, Yuzuki, can I take you to my place for now?
This is all my fault...
Huh?
I was the one who made her battle.
Well, yeah, but you just wanted to help, right?
Even though the truth was more than Hitoi could take, your intentions were still noble.
Thank you, Ruko.
Ah, I just realized this will be the second time you've stayed over.
Oh, um, actually, before we go back, can we stop somewhere for a sec?
Is this good? Can you see from here?
Yeah.
Well, if it isn't Yuzuki and Kazuki, are you stepping out?
Just to the convenience store.
Looks like we've got snow coming, so be careful.
Yes, ma'am.
See you later.
Yuzuki, something bothering you?
No.
What's this about?
I want to be boyfriend and girlfriend.
This is the only time we can be together as lovers.
Mom and dad are still upstairs watching TV.
No one from school's here to see us.
In weather like this, if we happen to share an umbrella, no one will bat an eye, right?
No one from school's home.
What?
What now?
Oh, isn't it beautiful, Kazuki?
Snowing just for us.
You really are strong, huh?
You've been like that ever since we were little.
You always protected me, kept me on the right path.
I should have told you.
For my entire life, I've loved you.
Thank you, but I want to protect you now, as your brother and your boyfriend.
Hmm.
She made my wish come true, didn't she?
Even though she took my body, she still kept her word.
Thank you, Hana-yo.
You were my friend.
You still...
Setting your little plan into motion, are you?
That's right.
I wonder. You think she'll really come?
Oh, don't worry. She'll come.
She's the same as me.
I suppose that's true.
And by that, I mean you both have Wecross on the brain and not much else.
Nothing personal, of course.
Though I wonder if two of you might be one too many.
That doesn't matter. She's my friend.
If I have to sacrifice her, then I might as well just disappear.
We're all still friends.
She made my wish come true, didn't she?
Even though she took my body, she still kept her word.
If my wish came true, then my wish.
Oh, Ru. Is something the matter?
Uh, no, I'm fine. Just spacing out.
So what are you up to out here, Grandma?
Nothing exciting. It started to snow, so I'm trying to dry off the potatoes I left outside.
Here, let me help.
Hey, Grandma.
Hmm.
All my life, I never really wanted to be anything or do anything, and I didn't really care if I had friends or not.
I guess that's not really normal, so I can't blame you for worrying.
But I've changed my mind now.
Hmm.
I made friends and realized I was wrong.
We had fun. I was happy.
I wanted to...
I mean, I want to stay with them forever.
So, I mean...
I guess what I'm asking is if there's anything I can do for them.
Hmm.
I'm sure you'll come up with something on your own.
Huh?
I have faith.
You are my Ru, after all.
You can do anything.
Uh...
Grandma.
Now let's see.
Guess we can't put them back outside.
No, but maybe over there, where they can still get some sun.
Okay.
Toma?
You're acting weird. What's wrong?
I wonder if you were like me when you were a real girl.
Bet you had all sorts of friends back then.
It'd be fun to find out what kind of wish you...
Stop it!
I don't know, okay?
I don't remember any of that stuff.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know that other stuff, either.
Not about selector switching with L-Rigs or wishes or the weird room.
I wouldn't lie to you.
Please believe me, Ru.
I just wanted to battle together.
I promise.
Of course I believe you.
You mean it?
Uh-huh.
You're my friend.
We have to trust each other.
I guess you were right.
It sure has been a long day, huh?
I'm going to bed.
Night-night, Toma.
Hey, did you see this?
Yeah, the Iona fan event thing, right?
Huh?
But on the ad, it said it's only for select people.
Do you have to win a contest or something?
It didn't seem like it, but I don't know.
There's no address listed, either.
It doesn't list anything but a contact.
Oh, yeah.
I sent them an email about it, but I didn't get a reply.
What the heck?
Ruko!
We gotta find that thing.
Do a search for it.
Uh-huh.
Try typing Iona fan event.
Uh, right.
What is it, Ru?
An Iona fan event, just like they said.
To those who are forced to select, to those who do not refuse to select, then it has hashtag
selector at the bottom.
So what do you guys think she's trying to do?
She's calling us out.
She's bringing the selectors together.
Iona fan event, just like they said.
It's happening really close to here, too.
Is something wrong?
I don't want to hear it, and I have nothing to say to you.
I'm sure my plan is going to work.
No, I don't want to!
I finally thought of a wish.
Next time, the summer of dreams.